孩子们  当你们都 快30岁的时候  可能会惊讶的
Kids, when you reach your late 20s you might be surprised
发现你还是搞不懂生活是什么
to discover you still don't have life quite figured out.
就像莉莉阿姨一样
Like with Aunt Lily.
即使她是从旧金山回来的
Even though she was back from San Francisco,
她仍然还在寻找自我
she was still on a quest to find herself.
我不想当幼儿园老师了
It's just that all I've ever done is teach kindergarten.
我要辞职  我要改变世界
I want to get out there and change the world.
我要找回自己的激情
I want to find my passion.
她也确实做到了
And she did find it.
我要去当个人生指导师
I'm going to be a life coach.
事实上  她的热情源源不断
In fact, she found it again and again.
我要去当个海洋生物学家
I'm going to be a marine biologist.
行为诗人...养蜂人...
...slam poet. ...beekeeper!
我不想当养蜂人了
Not a beekeeper.
她最新的人生梦想呢?
Her newest lifelong dream?
朋克风格乐队的主唱
Singing in a punk rock band.
那她钱哪里来的啊?
What is she doing for money through all this?
她在餐馆当服务生
Oh, she's been waiting tables at Big Wave Luau.
难道是在那个夏威夷风格的餐馆?
Wait, you mean that Hawaiian place
服务生穿着夏威夷的草裙
where they wear those embarrassing outfits?
不可能
No.
她来啦　她来啦
Here she comes. Here she comes.
欢迎光临  你们现在点菜吗?
Welcome to Big Wave Luau. May I tiki your drink order?
晕  混蛋
Aw, crap.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你好  莉莉 我们正好在附近
Oh, hi, Lily. We were just in the neighborhood,
想找个地方吃饭 但我们不知道原来你在这
thought we'd get some lunch. We didn't even know you'd be here.
要吃什么?
What do you want?
不会吧 你就这样在餐馆里...
Oh, I don't think that's how you're supposed to greet
招待客人吗?
a customer at Big Wave Luau.
你好  游客们 (夏威夷语)
Aloha, island visitors.
浪花把你们带到 我们这简陋的餐厅
The big wave brought you to our humble luau.
因此我们要用我们的母语说  谢谢 (夏威夷语)
For that, we thank you. Or in my native tongue, mahalo.
我没听清楚你的名字 你们听清了吗?
I didn't catch your name. Did you guys catch her name?
没有
No.
我叫阿努花
My name is Anuhea.
它的意思是 凉爽  芬芳
It means cool and fragrant,
就像我们餐馆的12种特色饮料
much like any of our 12 specialty drinks.
罗宾  你还要点什么吗?
Robin, nothing to add?
不要了  莉莉是我的朋友 我不会因为她为了实现梦想
No. Lily is my friend and I'm not going to make fun of her
而去取笑他
for trying to follow her dreams.
谢谢 (讽刺的口气)
Thank you.
但是可能你要拿出你的夏威夷鼓来
Although, you might want to bring out the big Hawaiian drum
因为今天就是我的生日
because I'm pretty sure today's my birthday.
生日快乐!
Birthday girl!
本字幕由www.YYETS.com
老爸老妈的浪漫史 第二季 第六集
翻译：   雨亦奇 校对：  叶 煦
后期：  oliver0951   字幕监制：叶煦
我今天特别想喝酒
I have never needed beer more than I do right now.
我以为你这学期的论文 简单的就象吃块蛋糕
I thought you said your semester was gonna be a piece of cake.
我记得是因为你说 这话的时候就在吃蛋糕
I remember because you were eating a piece of cake at the time
然后你说 "哥们  这学期的论文就这么简单"
and you said, "Dude, my semester is gonna be this."
是啊  本来会是这样
Yeah, well, it was supposed to be,
但是我的教授 是我有史以来见过最严格的
but my professor's like the toughest grader I've ever seen.
她今年夏天刚离了婚
She had like a bad divorce this summer
现在开始在我们身上发泄了
and now she's taking it out on us.
老实说  我觉得她只是需要男人
To tell you the truth, I think she just needs to get laid.
真的?
Really?
男人  你意思是?
Laid, you say?
你不会对她有兴趣? 她已经快五十了...
You wouldn't be into her. She's, like, in her late 40s.
她漂亮吗?
She hot?
有点漂亮吧?
Yeah, I guess she's kind of hot, yeah.
而且她很饥渴...
And she's looking for some action.
对我来说 她就是只饥饿的美洲豹
Sounds to me like she could be a cougar.
- 什么来着 - 美洲豹
- A what? - A cougar.
一个单身老女人 经常在她四十  五十岁时候
An older woman, usually in her 40s or 50s,
经常会去寻觅些年轻男人
single and on the prowl for a younger man.
那六十  七十岁的女人 是什么来着? 海龟?
What's a woman in her 60s or 70s-- a turtle?
马修  我想过了 我接受这个挑战
Marshall, I've thought it over and I accept your challenge.
- 我没让你去和她上床啊 - 明天  猎豹行动开始
- I didn't challenge you to have sex... - Tomorrow, the cougar hunt begins.
我要辞职了
So, I quit my job.
我受不了了
I just couldn't take it anymore.
每天大概有五十个男人向我要花环
Approximately 50 times a day, some guy asks me for a lei...
你太有才了
Classic.
泰德  你刚才不是跟我 说你们办公室需要一个助理?
Ted, didn't you tell me they need a new assistant in your office?
是啊
Yeah.
有人刚刚辞职了
Somebody did just quit.
我们中午哪里吃?
So, where should we eat today?
太好了 你给大家都买中饭了?
Oh awesome, you brought lunch for everyone?
你这也太不厚道了
Dude,  that is cold-blooded.
我很无辜的
It was an honest mistake.
你要是看到 一个人的盘子里有一整只鸡
Look, when somebody opens up a container with an entire chicken in it,
想当然就以为 是给大家准备的
it's okay to assume they made lunch for everyone.
你也太打击那个女孩子了
Ted, that girl didn't quit. You destroyed her.
那是一整只鸡啊
It was an whole chicken.
我有没有说过她是十二面型的
And did I mention she had 12 sides?
你现在又开始挑剔 她的体形了 你也太过分了
Oh, now you're gonna bash her figure. Real classy, Ted.
莉莉  你怎么样 想要那个工作吗?
So, Lily, what do you say? Do you want the job?
我需要做什么吗?
What would I be doing?
你是个一般的办公室助理
Basically, you're sort of a general office assistant.
你只要坐在那里 就在我的对面
You'll sit there. My station is right over here.
现在这里有些疯狂
And things are a little bit crazy right now
因为我们正在给 一个大客户设计一个建筑
'cause we're pitching a new building to a big client.
- 是那个吗? - 对
- Oh, right, is that the... - Yeah.
这是模型
Here's the model.
你不会是开玩笑 这看起来象一个巨大的小弟弟
You weren't kidding. It really does look like a giant penis.
我知道
I know.
德拉泽先生就是看不出来 (双关 偏爱的音译)
For whatever reason, Mr. Druthers just doesn't see it.
你怎么会看不出来?
How can he not see it?
- 你看  那里有... - 我知道
- I mean there's the... - I know.
- 而且这位置... - 我知道
- And the way it... - I know.
- 还有那两个小... - 我知道
- And the two little... - I know.
- 这真是... - 壮观?
- Wow, it is just... - Spectacular?
谢谢
Why, thank you.
莉莉  这是德拉泽先生 这个工程的主设计师
Lily, this is Mr. Druthers, the head architect on the project.
莉莉是办公室的新助理
Lily's going to be our new office assistant.
- 哦 - 很高兴认识你
- Ah. - Nice to meet you.
是吗?
Isn't it?
我看过了你设计的屋顶阳台
Ted, I looked at your design for the penthouse balcony.
告诉我 你是不是想要当设计师
Tell me, do you want to be an architect?
我  嗯... 我就是一个设计师啊
I, uh... I am an architect.
真的吗?
Really?
我的六岁的侄子喜欢玩积木
Well, my six-year-old nephew plays with Legos.
他算是个设计师?
Is he an architect?
不能算 除非他通过了所有的资格考试
Well, not unless he somehow passed all his licensing exams.
你很有前途
Ted, you've got promise.
但是你必须要更认真的向我学习
But you have to study what I do more carefully.
现在我要你给这个模型
Now I want you to design some Styrofoam trees
设计一些塑料的树
for the building model.
- 你能做到吗? - 当然
- Think you can handle that? - Absolutely.
很好  你是要去设计
Good. So you're going to design the...
- 塑料树 - 再说一遍  有精神点
- Styrofoam trees. - Once again-- with feeling.
- 塑料树 - 塑料树
- Styrofoam trees. - Styrofoam trees!
- 塑料树 - 这才算有精神
- Styrofoam trees! - That's the spirit.
现在　过来点
Now, gather 'round.
这已不单单是树了 这是生命...
This isn't just about trees, Ted. This is about life.
而且现在 你必须把这些树设计到位
And sometimes in life, you have to get the trees just right
否则你就要开除掉  懂吗?
or you're fired, hmm?
这人简直就是个...(混蛋  Lily指着洁宝形状的模型)
Man, that guy is a total, well...(Dick)
这就是路易斯教授的办公室
Okay, wait, wait, wait. That's Professor Lewis's office there.
我们去看看
Okay, let's take a look.
这就是一只美洲豹
Oh, yeah, it's a cougar all right.
典型的
A prime specimen.
凭几个特征你 就能看出她是只美洲豹?
See, you can identify a cougar by a few key characteristics.
看头发
Start with the hair.
美洲豹留着流行的发型
The  cougar keeps up with current hairstyles
作为一种伪装
as a form of camouflage.
这样她的猎物 就不会以为碰上了美洲豹
The prey may not realize that he's engaged a cougar
直到他无助地被美洲豹
until he's already being dragged, helpless,
拖回到他的窝
back to her lair.
现在  看她的上衣
Now, the blouse.
她会尽量的展示她的乳沟
The cougar displays maximum cleavage possible
来迷惑她的猎物
to captivate her prey.
如果你真的盯着它看
If you're watching them bounce,
那她就要准备捕杀你了
she's about to pounce.
看到她的爪子了吗?
See the claws?
又长又锋利
Long and sharp,
足以赶走她的竞争者
to ward off rival females...
也能开赡养费的支票
or open alimony checks.
这只真的很正点
Yeah, this one's a beaut.
猎豹行动开始
Okay, let the hunt begin.
等等  等等... 我好像有点无法接受
Wait, wait, wait. I'm not so sure I'm comfortable
你去泡我的宪法学教授
with you hunting my constitutional law professor.
你愿意谁来给你的论文打分
Who do you rather have grading your papers--
一只野蛮的  饥渴的野猫
a savage, man-eating jungle cat,
还是只娇喘着的 满足了的猫咪?
or a purring, satisfied kitty?
上吧  巴尼
Go, Barney.
用你的身躯填饱那只饥饿的美洲豹
Go mount and stuff that cougar.
苏茜  我是路易 意大利的交换生
Scusi, I am Luigi, Italian exchange student.
我本来是要去教室的
I was, uh, walking to class,
但是忽然我看到了你...
but then I noticed you...
美丽的公主...
bella  principessa...
你要什么还是自己滚蛋?
Tell me what you want or get out.
真直接
Direct.
我喜欢这样
I like that.
我名字叫巴尼
The name's Barney.
我要的是...你
What I want... is you.
转身
Turn around.
我那里...两小时
My place. Two hours.
不要迟到
Don't be tardy.
我不敢相信 德拉泽先生竟然这么凶
I can't believe how Mr. Druthers treats people.
还有那个建筑设计 言语难以形容
And that building? Talk about overcompensating.
他平时没这么凶
He's not usually this bad.
这次是因为我们的合作者说的很明白
It's just that the partners have made it very clear
成败就在这个项目上
this project is make or break for us,
所以最近他有点暴躁
so lately he's been a little testy.
Testy音近testis睾丸,暗指Ted公司的建筑模型
你们明白我的意思 想入非非...
You know what I mean-- crotchety.
Crotchety音近crotch胯下
我只是觉得最近他有点艰难
I'm just saying it's been hard on him.
Hard,这个不用多说了吧
好  够了  不说了
All right stop.
- 你给莉莉看过你的设计? - 还没
- Did you show Lily your design? - No.
- 什么设计? - 没什么
- What design? - It's nothing.
你的设计太好了
It's fantastic.
最近一直在忙他的设计
Just for fun, Ted's been working on his own design.
这个设计看起来 不太象个小弟弟
And it doesn't look at all like male genitalia.
至少不是健康的小弟弟
At least, not healthy male genitalia.
你应该把你的设计个德拉泽先生看看
Ted, you should pitch your building to Druthers.
你开玩笑? 他是汉默・德拉泽
Are you kidding? He's Hammond Druthers.
传奇人物 我只不过是他团队里的一员
He's a legend. I'm just part of his team.
这个设计对公司来说很重要
This building is huge for the firm,
所以现在我们千万不能搞砸了
so it's really important we don't blow it.
blow也有吹箫的意思..你懂得
好了  够了
All right, enough.
天那  难以置信
Oh, my God. Incredible.
你的分数是C-
Hmm... C-minus.
才C-? 你说什么?
C-minus? What are you talking about?
我可是干了一个通宵啊!
I just pulled an all-nighter!
你没有分配好你的时间
You didn't budget your time well,
你忽略了一些很重要的部分
you glossed over some of the most important points,
而且你的嘴功太差
and your oral presentation was sloppy and inconclusive.
德拉泽先生要我问你 你是不是在做树了?
Mr. Druthers asked if you were making the trees
还是在等它们自己发芽长大
or waiting for them to sprout on their own.
然后他就一直盯着我 看着我发笑
Then he stared at me until I laughed.
好了  完成了
Okay, I'm done.
太好了  我把这些颜料收拾下 你去拿给他看
Great. I'll put the paints away. You just go show him.
好  谢谢
Great. Thanks.
终于来了
Well, finally.
我在想你在做树呢
I wondered whether you were making the trees
还是在等它们自己发芽长大
or waiting for them to sprout on their own.
这笑话真好笑
Good one, sir.
你看一下这些模型
Anyway, here they are.
- 太绿了 - 太绿了?
- Too green. - Too green?
叶子应该有一种天然的褐色
Yes, the leaves should really be more of a natural brown color.
接近深褐色
Almost brunette.
想想灌木丛  我想要这个建筑
And think bushier. I want this tower to rise
耸立在一片浓密 原始的深褐色的丛林之中
from a thicket of wild, ungroomed, brunette shrubbery.
这几句Ted老板说的又可理解为那个洁宝形状建筑的阴毛(棕色的....汗...)
你能想象  泰德?
Can you picture it, Ted?
我不可能想象不出来?
I can't un-picture it.
很好
Good.
天哪
Oh, my God.
它不见了
It's gone!
什么?什么不见了?
What? What's gone?
有三个彼特・罗斯签名的棒球 (著名的击球手)
My baseball signed three times by Pete Rose.
它应该在办公室的某个地方?
Well, it's got to be around here somewhere.
你是这么认为的?
What do you think, Ted,
棒球自己溜了出来 然后滚到了某个地方?
it just let itself out of its plastic case and rolled away?
有人偷了它
Somebody stole it.
我得回去继续弄塑料树了
Well, um, I better get back to these Styrofoam trees.
谁会在意那些树
Oh, who cares about the trees?
这只不过是给你个差 让你觉得自己还用
It's just busy work to make you feel like you're contributing.
你总是在鼓励我
Inspiring as always, sir.
莉莉
Lily?
她把颜料放哪了?
Where's she put those paints?
Hey.
莉莉  问你点事
Hey. Um, Lily, question for you.
为什么我在你的抽屉里
Why did I find Mr. Druthers' baseball
找到了德拉泽先生的 有三个彼特・罗斯签名的棒球?
signed three times by Pete Rose in your desk drawer?
很简单　我拿的
That's easy. I took it.
为什么
Why?
很简单
It's simple.
为什么牛排上面没有黑胡椒汁?
I can't believe there's no horseradish for the roast beef.
你是不是  不会做三明治?
I guess you were sick the day they taught that at Sandwich University.
妈妈  疗养院的人没偷你的钱
Mother, no one from the nursing home is stealing from you.
我没给你买生日礼物
I didn't get you a birthday present.
什么  你不哭?
What? You gonna cry?
鼻涕虫怎么不哭?
Little  crybaby's going to cry?
大家看啊
Hey, everybody, look!
鼻涕虫要哭鼻子啦
The little crybaby's gonna cry!
我掉了冰激凌
I lost my ice cream!
最后一个我有可能夸张了点
Okay, I may have exaggerated that last one,
但重点是　他太低劣了
but the point is, he was mean.
因此我就偷了他的棒球(ball还有睾丸的意思)
And that's why I took away his ball.
但他的棒球和这没关系啊
What does his ball have to do with anything?
德拉泽要学会厚道
Druthers has to be taught he can't behave like that.
我在幼儿园的时候 孩子们一调皮
When I was teaching kindergarten, whenever a kid was mean,
我就拿走他们的玩具
I would take away one of his toys.
刚开始孩子们会不高兴
The kid would be upset at first,
然后他们就不调皮了
but then he'd learn to stop being mean.
伙计们　怎么啦?
Hey, guys. What's going on?
莉莉偷了我老板的 有三个彼特・罗斯签名的棒球
Lily stole my boss' baseball signed three times by Pete Rose.
为什么　因为他很低劣?
Why? Was he being mean?
- 你怎么知道 - 当然了
- You know about this? - Yeah.
这是她替天行道的方式
It's her own personal form of justice.
你告诉过他我们在Gap专卖店的故事吗
Did you tell him about that time at the Gap?
对　那是个好例子
Oh, that was a good one.
那个售货员对罗宾很凶
This sales guy was rude to Robin,
所以我就偷了件卡其裤
so I took a pair of khakis.
我把它当生日礼物送给了你
I gave them to you for your birthday.
然后我稀里糊涂卷进了偷窃案
So I've been walking around in stolen khakis?
我更喜欢叫它公道
I prefer to call them "justice khakis."
这不是公道　这是偷窃 这是犯罪
That's not justice. It's shoplifting, and it's a crime.
这也只不过是不厚道
So is being mean.
莉莉　你的办法行不通
Lily, your little system doesn't even make sense.
在幼儿园里 孩子们知道为何他们要被惩罚
In kindergarten, the kid knew why he was being punished.
德拉泽会认为是偷窃
Druthers just thinks someone stole his ball.
这就是为什么我留了个字条
Well, that's why I left a note.
- 字条? - 是
- A note? - Yeah.
他看到字条 就会知道为什么棒球不见了
When  he finds it, he'll understand why his ball was taken away,
他就会学着厚道点
he'll stop being mean,
办公室也会清静点
and the office will be a nicer place to work.
也许他还会听取点别人的意见
Maybe he'll even be open to hearing your ideas.
听着　莉莉 我们一直在忍受
Look, Lil, we're all tolerating
朋克乐队　养蜂人 还有那些小偷小摸
this prolonged nervous breakdown you're clearly having,
这些无理取闹
with the punk band and the beekeeping and the petty larceny,
但这次你不能把我的工作当儿戏
but this is my career you're messing with.
我不喜欢你这么对我说话
I'm not sure I like your tone.
你知道吗
You know what?
现在球你就甭想拿回去了
Now you just lost the ball.
Hey.
我想知道你昨晚进展的怎样 今天考了一次试
I'd ask you how last night went, but we had a pop quiz today.
大家的分数都在C-以下
Nobody got higher than a C-minus.
我就知道
I know, I know.
你一直说自己经验丰富
You claim to have so much sex.
我还真的以为　你是个行家呢
I only assumed you'd be good at it.
我失算了
Look, I miscalculated.
我以为她以为老了 不中用了  像大多数"美洲豹"
I thought she'd be old and fragile, like most cougars.
没想到她还这么勇猛
But kitty's got claws.
但是不用担心
Don't worry though.
今晚　我再去见她
Tonight, I'm seeing her again.
算了吧　哥们 你会让事情更糟
Just let it go, man. You're making things worse.
我保证　今晚之后 这只美洲豹会温顺的想只猫咪
I promise you, after tonight, that cougar will be my pet,
而我　就是她的主人
and I its master.
我想我是爱上你了
I think I'm falling in love with you.
这不会是你的第一次吧
Oh, God. That wasn't your first time, was it?
这样就说的通了
Although that would explain a lot.
什么　我们昨天还上过床啊
What? No. We had sex yesterday.
可能吧
Oh, right. That.
你昨天跟人上了床
Well, you had sex yesterday.
而我在修正你上床的课程摘要
I revised my syllabus for the spring semester.
德拉泽取拿面包的时候
When Druthers goes to get his bagel,
我就进办公室　拿走纸条 把棒球放回去
I'll go in, grab the note, put the ball back.
如果有什么意外的话
If something goes wrong,
你就说　谁要蒸馏咖啡
yell out, "Who wants espresso?"
这样我就知道他要过来
so I'll know he's coming. Got it?
好　现在把球给我
Okay, now give me the ball.
- 不 - 你这是什么意思?
- No. - What do you mean, no?
我要坚持我的原则
I mean I stand by what I did, Ted.
行行好　莉莉 我们快没时间了
Come on, Lily. We're running out of time.
大家都过来!
Everybody get in here now!
谁要蒸馏咖啡?
Who wants espresso?
大部分人应该都知道
Now, as most of you know,
我那有三个彼特・罗斯 签名的棒球不见了
my Pete Rose, Pete Rose, Pete Rose baseball has been stolen.
我刚才看到一张纸条
Well, I just found this note.
亲爱的德拉泽先生 我...你的棒球　现在走了
"Dear Mr. Druthers, I, your baseball, am leaving.
如果你现在开始学好的话 那我还会回来
Maybe, if you start being nice, I'll come back.
如果不　你办公室里的 其他东西也会象我一样走掉
If not, other things in your office may follow my lead.
事实上　我无意中 听到你的iPod说
In fact, I overheard your iPod talking,
它随时可能走掉
and he may shuffle off at any minute."
我会对着你们吼到我发不出声来
Normally, I would scream at everyone until my voice goes,
但是　在这里可能不妥
but maybe that's the wrong reaction here.
有意思
Interesting.
我给你们个机会 如果到今天晚上
Instead,  I'm giving my baseball until the end of the day
我的棒球还没有回家的话
to decide he's homesick,
那明天早上 我会在一小时内开除三个人
or, tomorrow morning, I'll begin firing three people an hour.
如果那个贼不相信
And, if the thief doesn't believe me, well,
那你这次下的赌注
then you are gambling more than Pete Rose--
就得比彼特・罗斯 联盟历史上伟大的击球手
major league baseball's all-time hit leader,
他没有被选入名人堂 这对整个体育界来说
a man whose absence from the Hall of Fame is a travesty
都是个悲剧...还要大
to the entire sports world-- ever "allegedly" did!
看起来他要跟iPod说拜拜了
Wow. Looks like bye-bye, iPod.
马上把棒球放回去
Give him his ball back right now.
别人会因你而开除的
People are going to get fired.
不会的 刚才他只是发了下飙
No, they're not. It's just a tantrum, Ted.
幼儿园里　我经常看到这样
I saw this in kindergarten all the time.
这里不是幼儿园
This isn't kindergarten.
德拉泽是个大人 他要他的棒球
Mr. Druthers is an adult, and he wants his ball back.
如果你把你的计划给他看 我就放回去
All right, I'll give it back if you show him your plans.
不行　要么你放回去 要么你被开除
No. You'll give it back or you're fired.
对不起　泰德 我不会这么做的
I'm sorry, Ted. I just can't do that.
那你被开除了
Then you're fired.
好的
Fine.
给你球
Here's the ball.
现在你至少有一个赌注了(Lily这里讽刺Ted没种把自己的设计给Boss看)
At least you have one now.
哥们　你整死我了
Dude, you're killing me.
你没搞定那只母豹 还把她惹怒了
You didn't tame the cougar. You just made her angrier.
你没看到我在吃PowerBar (一种运动营养品)
Do you not see the PowerBar in my hand?
我正在给自己充电
I'm fueling up.
你今晚还要过去?
So you're going back over there?
当然了
Oh, yeah.
今晚  我就是约翰・梅伦坎普 (摇滚歌手  中名是美洲豹)
And tonight, just like John Mellencamp,
我要彻底的征服那只美洲豹
I am going to get rid of the "Cougar" once and for all.
懂我的意思?
Get it?
约翰把自己的名字改成了美洲豹
'Cause that's what he did with his name.
我没办法不想你
I can't stop thinking about you.
请再给我次机会吧
Please give me another chance.
巴尼　我白天都要教书
Barney, I teach all day.
这是回家最后才干的事情
It's the last thing I want to do when I get home.
但是你不知道 以前我还没有全力以赴
But you don't understand. See, I've been going easy on you,
让开　不然你会摔破屁股的
holding back, 'cause I was afraid you'd break a hip or something.
这一次　我不会再心慈手软了 我不管这次是不是要干上
But, this time, no mercy. I don't care how long it takes--
几天　几个星期　还是半年
days, weeks, half a year.
好吧  进来吧
Fine. Come in.
等我改好这些论文 你才能开始
You can start while I finish grading some papers.
抓紧点　客户随时回来
Hurry up. Clients will be here any moment.
把这个放近点
Now, slide it closer to his chair.
我们的设计会让他大吃一惊
I want this thing to really smack him in the face.
德拉泽先生 谢谢你能理解莉莉
Mr. Druthers, thank you again for understanding about Lily.
其实我很同情她
Oh. Well, I pity her.
从我办公室偷走了 棒球还写下这么可笑的字条
I mean, to steal from my office and then write that slanderous note...
你说下　莉莉脑子有毛病
You might say that Lily was mentally deranged.
请你说下泰德
You might say that, Ted.
莉莉脑子有毛病
Lily was mentally deranged.
你最好说的大声点 让每个人都听到
You might even say it loud enough for everyone to hear.
莉莉脑子有毛病!
Lily was mentally deranged!
这话好像有点过分吧 你说呢　泰德
Oh! That's a bit harsh, don't you think, Ted?
客户来了
The clients are here.
太好了　快请进来
Excellent. Bring them in.
我们的客户是斯波坎市 一家大型银行和金融服务公司
Our client was a major bank and financial services company in Spokane.
他们想要一座 能体现东西部风情历史
They wanted a modern skyscraper that still captured
现代化大厦
the distinct flavor and history of the Northwest.
先生们　女士们 现在我给你们展示
Ladies and gentlemen, I give you
斯波坎市银行大厦
the Spokane National Bank Building.
这是小弟弟啊
That's a penis!
这...这太荒唐了
That's... that's ridiculous.
人们不可能 把这座宏伟的大厦当成...
There's no way this majestic tower can be confused
男性生殖器
with the male organ of love.
我们不会造这样的一座建筑
We're not building a penis.
你还有别的创意?
You got any other ideas?
别的创意?
Other ideas?
你说要汉默・德拉泽风格的建筑
You said you wanted Hammond Druthers.
这就是汉默・德拉泽风格
This is Hammond Druthers.
那我只能说再见了
Well, hats off to your ladyfriends,
我不会接受这个设计
but I'm not building it.
我们的合作结束了
We're done here.
如果不是那天我不小心 穿了莉莉的公道之裤
The trajectory of my entire career might have been different
我的人生轨迹可能会完全不同
had I not unwittingly worn my justice khakis that day.
等等
Wait!
我们还有个创意
We have one more idea for you.
泰德　你在干什么?
Ted, what are you doing?
我还有一个设计
I have another design.
坐下　马上闭嘴
Sit down, shut up right now.
不
No.
# Thank you for the invitation #
# She showed me very nice... #
我们敬下泰德 他可能是最年轻的
To Ted! The youngest person to ever design a building
70层大楼的设计师
over 70 stories probably!
可能!
Probably!
恭喜你　泰德
Congrats, Ted.
谢谢你告诉我 去反对德拉泽
Hey, thanks for telling me to stand up to Druthers
并提出自己的看法
and pitch my idea.
真的　没有你 这些都不可能发生
Seriously, none of this would have happened if it weren't for you.
你知道吗　泰德?
Oh. You know what, Ted?
这太棒了
That was very nice.
你现在可以把这些螺丝拿回去了
You have earned these screws back.
记得拧上螺丝以后 你的椅子才能坐
Don't sit in your desk chair until you've put them back in.
莉莉　我现在是项目经理
Hey, I'm project manager now,
所以　如果你想回来工作的话...
so, if you want your old job back...
不　谢谢了
No, thanks.
我知道我现在 我最适合干什么了
I think I figured out what I want to be when I grow up.
西赛　你可不能这么对小朋友
Casey, that's not how we treat people.
你不调皮　才能把这个拿回去
You'll get this back when you learn to be nice.
- 巴尼! 天那! - 怎么啦?
- Barney! Oh, my God! - What happened?
他摔了屁股
He broke his hip.
没那回事　我只是那里有点扭了
That's not true. It's just temporarily dislocated.
真的　我没事
Seriously, I'm fine.
他有事
No, he's not fine.
你好　路易斯教授
Professor Lewis, hi.
你好　埃里克森先生 今晚我改你的论文
Mr. Eriksen. Hello. I graded your paper tonight.
昨天我收到了一个惊喜
I was pleasantly surprised.
那当然了
Yeah, she was.
分数B+
B-plus.
才B+
B-plus?!
马修　等我八个星期的 理疗结束以后
Marshall, after I've gone through my eight weeks of physical therapy,
我去帮你拿个A回来
I am going to get you that "A"!
随便她吧
Let her go.
你驯服不了她
She belongs out there in the wild.
你应该感到庆幸的是
You should feel proud.
你和她搏斗过并活下来了
You fought the cougar and lived.
这真是趟神奇的经历
It was an amazing safari.
我迫不及待想给你看看照片
I can't wait to show you guys the slides.